<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Xss - Tag - w41bu1</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/xss/</link>
        <description>Xss - Tag - w41bu1</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>buivanyk4@gmail.com (w41bu1)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>buivanyk4@gmail.com (w41bu1)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 22:45:00 &#43;0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/xss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>CVE-2025-58990 Analysis &amp; POC</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/2025-10-05-cve-2025-58990/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 22:45:00 &#43;0700</pubDate>
    <author>buivanyk4@gmail.com (w41bu1)</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025-10-05-cve-2025-58990/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/app.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>A vulnerability in the ShopLentor plugin prior to version 3.2.0 allows an attacker with contributor privileges to inject malicious code into a block&rsquo;s CSS. This CSS is then loaded inline into the page and can lead to Stored XSS when previewed or rendered in a browser.
CVE ID: CVE-2025-58990 Product: WordPress ShopLentor Plugin Vulnerability Type: Cross Site Scripting Affected Versions: &lt;= 3.2.0 CVSS severity: Low (6.5) Required Privilege: Contributor Requirements Local WordPress and Debugging ShopLentor: v3.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>CVE-2025-27006 Analysis &amp; POC</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/2025-10-04-cve-2025-27006/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 19:37:00 &#43;0700</pubDate>
    <author>buivanyk4@gmail.com (w41bu1)</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025-10-04-cve-2025-27006/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/app.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>The vulnerability exists in the Authorsy plugin for WordPress prior to version 1.0.6. This could allow an attacker to inject malicious code (e.g., redirect scripts, ads, or other HTML payloads) into the website, which would execute when visitors open the page.
CVE ID: CVE-2025-27006 Product: WordPress Authorsy Plugin Vulnerability Type: Cross Site Scripting Affected Versions: &lt;= 1.0.5 CVSS severity: Medium (6.5) OWASP Top 10: A1: Broken Access Control Required Privilege: Subscriber Although the description requires Subscriber privileges, it can actually be exploited Unauthenticated.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>CVE-2025-53307 Analysis &amp; POC</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/2025-10-03-cve-2025-53307/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:19:00 &#43;0700</pubDate>
    <author>buivanyk4@gmail.com (w41bu1)</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025-10-03-cve-2025-53307/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/app.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>The vulnerability exists in the Assistant plugin for WordPress prior to version 3.6.2. This could allow an attacker to inject malicious code (e.g., redirect scripts, ads, or other HTML payloads) into the website, which would execute when visitors open the page.
CVE ID: CVE-2025-53307 Product: WordPress Assistant Plugin Vulnerability Type: Cross Site Scripting Affected Versions: &lt;= 1.5.2 CVSS severity: Medium (7.1) Required Privilege: Unauthenticated Requirements Local WordPress and Debugging Assistant: v1.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>CVE-2025-6234 Analysis &amp; POC</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/2025-10-02-cve-2025-6234/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:00:00 &#43;0700</pubDate>
    <author>buivanyk4@gmail.com (w41bu1)</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025-10-02-cve-2025-6234/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/app.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>The vulnerability exists in the Hostel plugin for WordPress prior to version 1.1.5.8. An attacker could exploit it to target high-privilege users like admins.
CVE ID: CVE-2025-6234 Product: WordPress Hostel Plugin Vulnerability Type: Cross Site Scripting Affected Versions: &lt; 1.1.5.8 CVSS severity: Medium (7.1) Required Privilege: Unauthenticated Requirements Local WordPress and Debugging Hostel Plugin: v1.1.5.7 (vulnerable) and v1.1.5.8 (patched) Diff tool: meld or any tool that can compare two versions Analysis The root cause is the lack of sanitization and escaping for a parameter before rendering it on the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
